Stop following me.
توقف عن اللحاق بي.
The target is too big.
الهدف كبير جدًا.
It's easy to be found.
من السهل العثور عليها.
I'll follow you.
سأتبعك.
I want to go in.
اريد الدخول.
What's wrong?
ما هو الخطأ؟
Only one person can stand here.
يمكن لشخص واحد فقط أن يقف هنا.
Look.
نظرة.
Well.
نحن سوف.
I'll leave then.
سأرحل بعد ذلك.
You.
أنت.
You're annoying
أنت مزعج
You're so clingy.
أنت متشبث جدا.
What if you get married?
ماذا لو تزوجت؟
If you don't follow me, I won't follow you.
إذا لم تتبعني ، فلن أتبعك.
Don't let me follow you after you get married.
لا تدعني أتبعك بعد الزواج.
Who wants to follow you?
من يريد متابعتك؟
Brother,
أخ،
your trick is really amazing.
خدعتك مذهلة حقًا.
Separate them.
تفصل بينهما.
And break them one by one.
وكسرهم واحدًا تلو الآخر.
Well,
نحن سوف،
It's like hunting.
إنه مثل الصيد.
I can't stop it.
لا أستطيع إيقافه.
Tonight is the full moon night.
الليلة هي ليلة اكتمال القمر.
It's also the time when we're done.
إنه أيضًا الوقت الذي ننتهي فيه.
Yes.
نعم.
Let those so-called noble families
دع تلك العائلات النبيلة يسمى
come down to accompany you tonight.
تعال لمرافقتك الليلة.
Use their blood
استخدم دمائهم
to cut the edge of Siyun Sword.
لقطع حافة سيف سييون.
So what Leng Wuyou said is true.
إذن ما قاله Leng Wuyou صحيح.
Really?
هل حقا؟
You said Tang Mu Feng took our sacrifice sword,
قلت أن تانغ مو فنغ أخذ سيف التضحية لدينا ،
did you make a mistake?
هل أخطأت؟
Absolutely not.
بالطبع لا.
Master Tang is such a nice person,
السيد تانغ شخص لطيف ،
and he treats us well,
وهو يعاملنا جيدًا ،
We have no grudges against him,
ليس لدينا ضغائن ضده ،
why would he do that?
لماذا فعل ذلك؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I don't believe it.
لا أصدق ذلك.
I'll leave now.
سأغادر الآن.
-Good afternoon. -Good
-طاب مسائك.  -حسن
afternoon.
بعد الظهر.
Master Tang,
سيد تانغ ،
we have no grudges in the long run and no grudges in the near future,
ليس لدينا ضغائن على المدى الطويل ولا ضغائن في المستقبل القريب ،
Please let me go.
أرجوك دعنى أذهب.
Master Tang,
سيد تانغ ،
I'm innocent.
أنا بريء.
Stop yelling.
توقف عن الصراخ.
No one will talk to you if you shout again.
لن يتحدث معك أحد إذا صرخت مرة أخرى.
I don't want it.
لا اريدها.
I'm going to shout,
سأصرخ ،
Master Tang.
سيد تانغ.
Stop yelling.
توقف عن الصراخ.
It's really noisy.
انها حقا صاخبة.
You might as well save your energy.
يمكنك كذلك توفير طاقتك.
Enjoy the happy time now.
استمتع بالوقت السعيد الآن.
Tang Mu Feng,
تانغ مو فنغ ،
we have no grudges.
ليس لدينا ضغائن.
Why did you plot against us?
لماذا تآمرت علينا؟
No grudges or enmity.
لا ضغائن ولا عداوة.
Then why don't you ask them,
ثم لماذا لا تسألهم ،
how did my brother die?
كيف مات اخي
Your brother committed suicide because of poor management of the Imperial Sword Villa,
انتحر أخوك بسبب سوء إدارة فيلا السيف الإمبراطوري ،
too much debt to pay off,
الكثير من الديون لسدادها ،
What does it have to do with us?
ما علاقة ذلك بنا؟
Bullshit!
هراء!
If you hadn't said that the quality of the swords sold in Imperial Sword Villa
إذا لم تقل أن جودة السيوف المباعة في Imperial Sword Villa
was questionable,
كان مشكوك فيه ،
How can the Imperial Sword Villa be poorly managed?
كيف يمكن إدارة فيلا Imperial Sword بشكل سيء؟
How could my brother kill himself?
كيف يمكن لأخي أن يقتل نفسه؟
The name Xiaoman
اسم شياومان
is familiar to you.
مألوف لك.
Xiaoman,
شياومان
that's right,
هذا صحيح،
As the female leader of Tiance Mansion,
بصفتها قائدة قصر تيانس ،
Situ has no worries.
الموقع ليس لديه مخاوف.
Xiaoman,
شياومان
what Xiaoman?
ما شياومان؟
Anyway, tonight
على أي حال ، الليلة
is the day of your blood sacrifice to my brother.
هو يوم ذبيحة دمك لأخي.
Master Tang.
سيد تانغ.
No.
لا.
Guards,
حراس،
Master,
يتقن،
Bring them here.
أحضرهم هنا.
I'm going to sacrifice my sword
سأضحي بسيفي
with their blood,
بدمائهم ،
Yes.
نعم.
Brother,
أخ،
it's time.
حان الوقت.
Our Imperial Sword Villa
لدينا فيلا السيف الإمبراطوري
will be able to regain the glory of the past soon.
سيكون قادرًا على استعادة مجد الماضي قريبًا.
We still need to build lots of houses
ما زلنا بحاجة إلى بناء الكثير من المنازل
to fulfill your wish.
لتحقيق رغبتك.
Brother,
أخ،
we made it.
لقد فعلناها.
You made it.
لقد فعلتها.
It must be a fine product
يجب أن يكون منتجًا جيدًا
produced by Imperial Sword.
من إنتاج Imperial Sword.
This feeling,
هذا الشعور،
this is what it feels like.
هذا هو الشعور.
Why hasn't the sacrifice been brought?
لماذا لم تقدم التضحية؟
Somebody!
شخص ما!
Stop yelling.
توقف عن الصراخ.
No one will talk to you
لن يتحدث معك أحد
even if you shout your throat out.
حتى لو صرخت حلقك.
you guys
شباب
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Don't worry about that.
لا تقلق بشأن ذلك.
You didn't expect that, did you?
لم تتوقع ذلك ، أليس كذلك؟
We saw through your scheme.
لقد رأينا من خلال مخططك.
Right?
حق؟
Really?
هل حقا؟
Do you think Tang Mu Feng wants to sacrifice our swords?
هل تعتقد أن تانغ مو فنغ يريد التضحية بسيوفنا؟
Is there a mistake?
هل هناك خطأ؟
It's absolutely impossible.
إنه مستحيل تمامًا.
Master Tang is such a nice person,
السيد تانغ شخص لطيف ،
and he treats us well,
وهو يعاملنا جيدًا ،
We have no grudges against him,
ليس لدينا ضغائن ضده ،
why would he do that?
لماذا فعل ذلك؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I don't believe it.
لا أصدق ذلك.
If Luo Chen doesn't believe it,
إذا لم يصدق لو تشن ذلك ،
I don't believe it either.
أنا لا أصدق ذلك أيضًا.
Xu Yinuo,
Xu Yinuo ،
what do you think?
ما رأيك؟
It's true.
انها حقيقة.
Tang Mu Feng, you scum,
تانغ مو فنغ ، أيها الحثالة ،
killed the landlady with Siyun Sword.
قتل صاحبة الأرض بسيف سيئون.
Now, the wife of shop-owner's body
الآن زوجة جثة صاحب المحل
is in his room.
في غرفته.
What?
لما؟
This scum killed the landlady.
قتل هذا حثالة صاحبة الأرض.
I must cut him
يجب أن أقطعه
into pieces,
إلى قطع
Calm down, okay?
اهدأ ، اتفقنا؟
Don't take revenge all the time,
لا تنتقم طوال الوقت ،
you little brat,
أيها الشقي الصغير ،
Are you scared?
هل انت خائف؟
Now Siyun Sword is bloodthirsty
الآن سيف سيون متعطش للدماء
and has become a magic sword.
وأصبح سيفا سحريا.
We are no longer Tang Mu Feng's match.
لم نعد مباراة تانغ مو فنغ.
Well,
نحن سوف،
What should we do then?
ماذا يجب ان نفعل بعد ذلك؟
It's not that
انها ليست التي
there's no way.
ليس هناك طريقة.
Just tell me.
فقط أخبرني.
That was a year ago.
كان ذلك قبل عام.
Tell me,
أخبرني،
Cut the crap.
قطع الفضلات.
Say it.
قلها.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
All right.
حسنا.
I'll cut to the chase.
سأقطع إلى المطاردة.
The only way to defeat Tang Mu Feng now,
الطريقة الوحيدة لهزيمة تانغ مو فنغ الآن ،
is to gather Qi Xun Yang,
هو جمع Qi Xun Yang ،
Two famous swords, Chasing the Moon.
سيفان مشهوران ، مطاردة القمر.
Now,
حاليا،
you have the Sun-seeking Sword,
لديك سيف البحث عن الشمس ،
As long as we find the Moon Chasing Sword,
طالما وجدنا سيف مطاردة القمر ،
we can defeat Tang Mu Feng and Siyun Sword.
يمكننا هزيمة Tang Mu Feng و Siyun Sword.
What are you waiting for?
ماذا تنتظر؟
Let's go.
لنذهب.
Keep the change.
احتفظ بالباقي.